<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"> <id>/</id><title>David Wolfe</title><subtitle>A space for creative and professional endeavors. Capture The Flag (CTF) WriteUps, HackTheBox WriteUps, Cyber Security blog posts. Learning all the time.</subtitle> <updated>2022-01-24T10:41:40-06:00</updated> <author> <name>David Wolfe</name> <uri>/</uri> </author><link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="/feed.xml"/><link rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en" href="/"/> <generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.1">Jekyll</generator> <rights> © 2022 David Wolfe </rights> <icon>/assets/img/favicons/favicon.ico</icon> <logo>/assets/img/favicons/favicon-96x96.png</logo> <entry><title>JohnTheRuler</title><link href="/posts/John_The_Ruler/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="JohnTheRuler" /><published>2022-01-24T10:00:00-06:00</published> <updated>2022-01-24T10:00:00-06:00</updated> <id>/posts/John_The_Ruler/</id> <content src="/posts/John_The_Ruler/" /> <author> <name>David Wolfe</name> </author> <category term="Tools" /> <category term="Web Based" /> <summary> Overview: This is a quick blog post to discuss a tool I’ve been developing over the past week or so. During a couple recent CTF competitions I found myself needing a quick and easy method of testing custom John The Ripper wordlist rules. I decided to recreate most of the important John rules and compiled it all into a javascript application that is hosted on my GitHub pages. Uses and Demos: I ... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>Kerberos Amusement Park</title><link href="/posts/Kerberos_Amusement_Park/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Kerberos Amusement Park" /><published>2021-11-22T09:00:00-06:00</published> <updated>2021-11-23T08:42:06-06:00</updated> <id>/posts/Kerberos_Amusement_Park/</id> <content src="/posts/Kerberos_Amusement_Park/" /> <author> <name>David Wolfe</name> </author> <category term="Writeups" /> <category term="IASG" /> <summary> Overview This is a quick blog post to discuss the talk I gave to Iowa State’s Information Assurance Student Group (IASG). The topic for my presentation was Intro to Kerberos. I’ve recently gone through several interviews in which I was asked for specifics of the Kerberos protocol and to walk through a couple of basic attacks. My goal for this presentation was twofold: Students should leave w... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>eXcellent encryption</title><link href="/posts/eXcellent_encryption/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="eXcellent encryption" /><published>2021-11-09T16:30:00-06:00</published> <updated>2021-11-09T16:30:00-06:00</updated> <id>/posts/eXcellent_encryption/</id> <content src="/posts/eXcellent_encryption/" /> <author> <name>David Wolfe</name> </author> <category term="Writeups" /> <category term="sp00kyCTF" /> <summary> Description: A witch put a spell on my flag! Can you help break this and get me my flag back so I can trade it for candy? Flag format: sp00ky{ This was a challenge I created for the Information Assurance Student Group’s anual sp00ky CTF Given information For this challenge players were given the hex bytes 00 1b 49 5a 0a 1a 10 14 39 1c 2b 15 3c 21 43 09 26 5a 0f 0d 05 2c 38 49 06 37 0a 05 14 ... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>CCanary</title><link href="/posts/CCanary/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="CCanary" /><published>2021-09-24T16:30:00-05:00</published> <updated>2021-09-25T09:45:35-05:00</updated> <id>/posts/CCanary/</id> <content src="/posts/CCanary/" /> <author> <name>David Wolfe</name> </author> <category term="Writeups" /> <category term="ALLES CTF" /> <summary> Description: I'm using arch btw... ¯\_(ツ)_/¯ For this challenge we are given both the compiled C file and the source code for the application. Static Analysis For starters, I ran the application a couple of times to ensure I knew what “normal operation” was for this program. These first runs of the program show a very simple interface where the user is prompted for input and then that input... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>Packed</title><link href="/posts/Packed/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Packed" /><published>2021-08-17T15:30:00-05:00</published> <updated>2021-08-18T14:30:51-05:00</updated> <id>/posts/Packed/</id> <content src="/posts/Packed/" /> <author> <name>David Wolfe</name> </author> <category term="Writeups" /> <category term="RACTF" /> <summary> Description: Our team wants to use this Really Awesome Console Application, but they don't want to pay for it. Can you help them crack it and generate a license key for the username John Smith? We are only given the program as a 32 bit EXE and the IP:Port of the real service. Static Analysis I started this challenge the way I start most pwn/reverse problems. Running it to get some idea of “no... </summary> </entry> </feed>
